Bijendra Gurung beowulfkin@gmail.com Linked In: bijendra-gurung-a6107710

Linked In: bijendra-gurung-a61977167 https://cv.bijendragurung.com.np/

Tokha, Kathmandu, Nepal Contact: 9745973000

Summary

A bachelor running, young, energetic, professional candidate having a previous working experience as data entry and marketing manager, willing to add organizational value through his domain expertise.

Professional Skills

- Communication & leadership
- Analytical & interpersonal skill
- Problem Solving & Typing
- MS Office & Excel
- Python & Java Programming

Experience

Data Entry (2018 to 2019)

Nepmandu International Education Pvt Ltd Baneshwor, Kathmandu

Accomplishments:

- Agent Form agreement
- Students Visa application form
- Documentation of students for abroad study

Marketing Manager Assistance (2020-2021)

Nepmandu International Education Pvt Ltd Baneshwor, Kathmandu

Accomplishments

- Dealing with Foreign agent
- Marketing and branding about Nepmandu Consultancy
- Evaluating marketing and digital marketing.

Intern

SNS Migration and Education (2022/07/01-2022/08/03) Putalisadak, Kathmandu Accomplishments

- Documentation
- Application Enrollment Form

Front Desk Officer (July 1, 2022, to August 3, 2022)

Overseas Friendship International Hospital Lekhnathmarg, Thamel, Kathmandu July 1, 2022, to August 3, 2022

Accomplishments

- Efficient Patient Check-In and Check-Out
- Enhanced Patient Communication
- Administrative Efficiency
- Accurate Data Management
- Enhanced Front Desk Operations

Customer Support Representative (2022 – Present)

Innovatetech (**mySecondTeacher**) Baluwatar, Kathmandu

Accomplishments

- Improved User Satisfaction
- Enhanced Communication Channels
- Feedback Collection and Analysis
- Training and Development
- Efficient Issue Resolution & Technical Troubleshooting
- Accurate Data Management

Education

School Leaving Certificate (2015)

Shree Adarsha Bal Secondary School Sundar Bazar, Lamjung

Intermediate (+2), Management (2016-2017)

Computer Science specialization Southwestern State College Basundhara, Kathmandu

Bachelor of Business Studies (2024- present)

Saraswathi Multiple Campus Lekhnathmarg, Thamel, 44600

Courses and Certification

- Artificial Intelligence (AI) Training (Feb 2022- May 2022), Broadway Infosys Nepal Pvt. Ltd, Shriganesh Marg, Kathmandu 44600
- Digital Skills: Digital Marketing(May 2022- June 2022), Future Learn
- Study UK: A guide to Education Agents(Jan 2022 -Feb2022), British Council.

Reference

Pratik Adhikari, Founder & CEO Nepmandu International Education Pvt Ltd Contact no.9851255263 New Baneshwor, Kathmandu, Nepal,

SNS Migration and Education Service Contact no. 015323933 Putalisadak, Kathmandu, Nepal

Dr. Prashant Mandal Overseas Friendship International Hospital Contact no. 9851127444 Lekhnathmarg, Thamel, Kathmandu